[{"answer": "No one will have seen it on state television and there's been no comment on state television about it.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "Did anyone see the speech where you are?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well, the way it's read here is that this is the international coalition, the crusader army, as Gadhafi puts it, coming in on the side of the opposition to rebuild the sort of colonial footprint here, divide the country, steal the oil.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "I mean the key thing, it seems to me, Nic, is we're still not really sure -- I don't think -- what this mission is, because there is a confusion between a position that says we don't want regime change, but we do want Gadhafi gone, isn't there?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "If that's the way this is going to take shape over the coming weeks and months, it's clearly going to be a very protracted affair, because the opposition really isn't in a place to face of against Gadhafi's army, even if you neutralize the army, their heavy weapons, their superiority, and advantage on the battlefield, what would seem today in Sirte, Gadhafi's hometown, is civilians with weapons.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "What did you make of that development in this story?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Parts of it are very good.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Senator, what did you make of the speech?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Here's what I do know.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "I mean is that the kind of rebel army that we should be supporting?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Well, here's what happened in Iran.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "But isn't that exactly what people were saying in Iran before they were indeed taken over by extremists?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I think so far so good.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "General Myers, from a military perspective, is it satisfactory and clear enough for the military leaders that you have the president saying we don't want regime change, but we do want Gadhafi gone?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "I think, Piers, we're going to learn a lot more as -- tomorrow, the next day, there's going to be a get-together in London, I think, to talk to some of the opposition leadership.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "I mean are these the kind of people that we can trust to be the stable future government of this country that we presumably believe they can be?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Well, that's the -- you know, that's always the question.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "If we assume the president is right when we he says this is a humanitarian exercise, then what happens if these rebels begin to turn their guns on pro-Gadhafi supporters who are civilians?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "I think it's a great speech.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "What do you think of the speech tonight?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think so there is any chance for Gadhafi to stay in power.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Where does that leave everybody?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "It leaves -- it leaves America, it leaves the Middle East, it leaves the world in a very -- in a very terrible situation.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "But right now, we're in a position where if Gadhafi hangs on, and America has not gone in with its full might, where does that leave everybody?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Let me play devil's advocate.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "How can you leave him there?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "I don't quite understand that.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "Would you be happy as American president to have seen in the way that we did very unusually the French taking the lead followed by the British, and the Americans, you know, sending most of the forces in terms of all these, you know, missiles being fired, but not wanting to have the credit for doing that?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "What happens if -- as we're seeing now in Syria, for example, you're seeing the leadership there killing large numbers of people, ever increasing numbers of people.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "If they're so darned upset about us being in the Middle East, why would they ask him to intervene?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "Yes, he did.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "P.J. Crowley, did he sell it to you?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "I mean Kosovo is a very good example of where we did a bombing for 79 days.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Do you think that the way this coalition has now been constructed is likely to be an effective one?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Well, if you look at Egypt, the fundamental decision -- why Egypt worked the way it was is because the Egyptian military, from the outset, said very clearly, we are not going to turn our weapons on our own people.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "Are you absolutely confident that what everyone assumes was going to happen in Benghazi is what was going to happen?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "Understand the predicates to military action.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Presumably, given that's what's happening in Syria and Yemen, you would want to go in there as well, would you?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "In fact, as Secretary Clinton and Secretary Gates said yesterday, the Middle East is, in fact, of vital interest to the United States.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "At what point does America stop meddling in Middle Eastern affairs and look after it's own backyard?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Do you stand by those comments?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "I felt that under the circumstances, given the way that the issue emerged, it was my best step to resign.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "So do you feel that you were treated unfairly?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Well, I think he's trying hard.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "What was your reaction to President Obama's speech tonight?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "It makes no sense whatsoever.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "When you hear President Obama say that he wants to get rid of Gadhafi, but he doesn't want regime change, does that make sense to you?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "That's a very good point.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "And why aren't they paying for this?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "Well, I felt that the president was very presidential tonight.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "As a matter of principle, is it sensible that America gets involved in what is clearly a civil war in Libya?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "Yes, look, I think the sign that the president's probably on the right path is his critics are criticizing him in the same interview for going too far and not going far enough and fast enough.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Anthony Weiner, do you agree with that assessment?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "That's exactly the point the president made about not being willing to get stuck in.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "If the Saudis and others are keen for America to step in and get rid of Gadhafi, why aren't they helping to pay for it?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "I guess you don't remember the Kosovo engagement of 1999.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "When you drop bombs on people, you're at war, aren't you?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "It's interesting when we're talking about stepping in, when in fact you have other countries that are making Libya look like nice guys.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "What is your take on the strength of America here?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Governor Richardson, let me come back to you.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Are we winning for people that are friendly with Iran or al Qaeda?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "Well, I was shaking my head at you as well.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "Why were you doing that?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Governor Richardson, the intriguing thing about Gadhafi is that, of course, until recently, we were back on friendly terms with this murderous dictator, weren't we?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Well, I think that's right, but I also say that NATO is us.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "As a businessman, what do you think?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "Anthony Weiner, you're still shaking your head.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Why aren't they paying us for it?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110328pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "If the Arab League now say we need you in Syria, do we go?", "qSentId": 569}]